familyshare.com 2017-08-30

# Privacy Statement

* ## General

* This website (the "Site") is operated by Deseret Digital Media, Inc. ("Operator"). The following Privacy Statement (the "Statement") supplements the Terms of Use posted elsewhere at the Site. By using the Site, you agree to be bound by all of the terms, conditions and notices contained or referenced in the Statement or the Terms of Use. You should review the Statement and the Terms of Use from time to time. Operator may change any portion of the Statement or the Terms of Use at any time without notice by posting revisions to the Site. Your continued use of the Site constitutes your acceptance of the revised Statement and the Terms of Use. If you do not accept all of the terms and conditions set forth in the Statement and the Terms of Use, you must exit the Site immediately.

* ## Registration

* The area of the Site that allows you to "sign in" or register is intended for individuals who are at least 13 years old. To "sign in" or register, you must provide your email address, create a password and confirm that you are at least 13 years old. YOU ARE NOT REQUIRED TO "SIGN IN" OR REGISTER TO USE THE SITE. THE DECISION TO "SIGN IN" OR REGISTER IS ENTIRELY VOLUNTARY ON YOUR PART AND IS MADE AT YOUR SOLE DISCRETION.

* ## What Information is Collected

* Operator collects information both actively and passively. For example, Operator will collect information about you that you voluntarily provide on the Site. In addition to information provided directly by you, Operator and third parties with features at the Site may collect aggregate information through the use of "cookies" or by other electronic means. In general, a cookie is a small amount of data sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. With most browsers or other software, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. You can refer to the instructions for your browser to learn more about these functions. If you choose to reject cookies, the Site likely will not operate as efficiently for you.

* ## No Information from Children under the Age of 13

* Operator does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 and does not wish to collect any such information. If Operator becomes aware that it has collected personal information from a child under the age of 13, Operator will delete the information immediately.

* ## Ownership and Use of Information

* Any information collected by Operator in connection with your use of the Site, regardless of whether collected actively or passively, will belong exclusively to Operator and may be used, maintained, updated OR disclosed by Operator as desired in its sole discretion. **OPERATOR MAY CHOOSE TO DISCLOSE NONPUBLIC PERSONAL INFORMATION ABOUT YOU, THE CONSUMER, TO A THIRD PARTY FOR COMPENSATION.**

* By agreeing to this Privacy Policy you agree to allow FamilyShare.com to send you third party email offers based on your interests.

* ## Links to Third Party Sites

* The Site may contain links to websites operated by third parties. These links do not constitute or imply an endorsement of any linked site. The linked sites may appear to be integrated into the Site, but are not under Operator's control. Operator is not responsible for the operation or content of any linked site or subsequent links from that site. The policies that govern the use of a linked site will differ from Operator's policies. You should review the policies of a linked site before making a decision to use that site.

* ## Contact Information

* Direct all questions or requests concerning the Statement or the Site to [support@familyshare.com](https://familyshare.com/mailto:support@familyshare.com)
